module.exports = {
  data: [
    {
      id: 1,
      question: 'In what sense is insurance intangible? How is the intent of the parties made tangible?',
      answer: 'Insurance is intangible; it is based on an exchange of promises. \n' +
          'The terms of the policy state what the insurer promises to do and what coverage it will provide and what the insured promises to do and what coverage they will receive. In short, the insurance policy is the document that makes tangible the intent of both parties to the contract.',
    },
    {
      id: 2,
      question: 'What is the principle of indemnity?',
      answer: 'The principle of indemnity is that the insured shall not receive more than the actual loss suffered.',
    },
    {
      id: 3,
      question: 'What is a fortuitous event?',
      answer: 'For a loss to be covered it must be fortuitous (a chance event).',
    },
    {
      id: 4,
      question: 'How is insurance a contract?',
      answer: 'Insurance is an agreement or promise between two parties, that is intended to be legally enforceable.',
    },
    {
      id: 5,
      question: 'What are the FIVE (5) elements that make up a contract under the common law in Canada?',
      answer: '1.\tAn Agreement\n' +
          '2.\tBetween legally capable parties\n' +
          '3.\tFor a consideration\n' +
          '4.\tDemonstrating intent\n' +
          '5.\tTo do something that is legal.',
    },
    {
      id: 6,
      question: 'How is a contract defined under the Civil Code of Quebec?',
      answer: 'An agreement of wills by which one or several persons obligate themselves to one or several other persons to perform a prestation (that is, a duty, a payment of money, or a service).',
    },
    {
      id: 7,
      question: 'How do insurance contracts differ from other types of contracts?',
      answer: 'Insurance policies differ from other types of contracts as they include the additional principles of:\n' +
          '-Indemnity\n' +
          '-Insurable interest\n' +
          '-uberrimae fidei, or utmost good faith',
    },
    {
      id: 8,
      question: 'What does uberrimae fidei stand for?',
      answer: 'Utmost good faith',
    },
    {
      id: 9,
      question: 'Why is utmost good faith essential for a binding insurance contract?',
      answer: 'It is the basis of all insurance contracts. It calls for the highest standards of integrity from the insured and the insurer. Both parties are bound to exercise good faith and do so by a full disclosure of all information material to the proposed contract.',
    },
    {
      id: 10,
      question: 'What is the purpose of the insurance contract?',
      answer: 'The insurance policy formalizes the agreement between the insured and insurer.',
    },
  ]
};
